You know it is your turn to be delivered.
It is your turn to be healed.
"It is my turn to be saved" - confess this right now!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Someone is busy to deliver you.
Hallelujah!
Open your lips.
Say to the Lord, "Take more of me and give me more of You".
Holy Spirit, take more of me and give me more of You.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Take more of me and give me more of You.
Holy Spirit, take more of me and give me more of You.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name.
Right now, open your lips and begin to release yourself.
Release yourself, in the name of Jesus.
Release yourself from every spirit that torments your career,
every spirit that torments your marriage,
every spirit that torments your business!
Every spirit!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Begin to release yourself!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I command you, that spirit -
you spirit that kills and destroys - I command you - leave my people!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I separate you from that spirit!
Be separated, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Let there be light!
Let there be light in your darkness!
Let there be light in your dark moment!
Let there be light!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Darkness is setback, disappointment, limitation, sickness, infirmity, failure, nightmare -
let there be light!
In your darkness, let there be light!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen. People are vomiting out poisonous substances from their system.
Overflow Congregation
That is the overflow section of the church.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus!
You command light into your challenges.
Your challenge is darkness.
Whatever challenges you have - be it sickness, disease, failure, nightmare, barrenness -
whatever challenges you have - begin to command light!
Let there be light!
In your setback, let there be light!
In your challenges, let there be light!
In your nightmare, let there be light!
In your setback, let there be light!
In your failure, let there be light!
In your disappointment, let there be light!
Let there be light!
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Watch your screen and see that woman vomiting out the poison in her system.
That is not just an ordinary saliva
but that is what satan had planted in her life to cause pain and discomfort.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Pray in the power of the Holy Spirit and see what is happening.
Whatever that is not planted by God is being uprooted from the lives of the people right now.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Whatever situation you are in is darkness.
Whatever situation you are facing is darkness.
Let there be light, in the name of Jesus!
Your situation is darkness.
Be it in your finances, relationships, marriage, health -
wherever it is located in your health, it is darkness.
Let there be light, in the name of Jesus!
Let there be light!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Command light!
Light dispels darkness.
Begin to command light!
Command light, in the name of Jesus!
Command light!
Viewers all over the world, whatever situation you are in,
whatever challenges - it is darkness.
I command light!
Let there be light, in the name of Jesus!
In your health - let there be light!
In your kidneys - let there be light!
In your liver - let there be light!
In your blood - let there be light!
In your organ - let there be light!
Wherever it is located - let there be light!
Let there be light!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
That setback - let there be light!
That disappointment - let there be light!
That failure - let there be light!
That infirmity - let there be light!
Let there be light!
That nightmare - let there be light!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see the light of God!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Confess the light of God.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Begin to confess the light of God!
In that fibroid, confess the light of God!
In that situation, confess the light of God!
In that cancer, confess the light of God!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In your blood, confess the light of God!
In your kidneys, confess the light of God!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, begin to check yourself because I am seeing you being healed!
I am seeing you being delivered!
Check yourself and testify.
Check yourself.
Testify to your testimony!
Say, "My problem has burst!"
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah!
Give thanks to Him.
Give thanks to God.
The Lord is good, all the time!
Overflow Congregation
Give thanks to God.
Give thanks to Him for delivering you.
Give thanks to the Deliverer.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
For those who believe they are not healed - I command you to be healed!
I command you to be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever the level of your faith, receive Jesus' faith, in the name of Jesus!
Here is faith to believe. Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever the level of your belief, here is the faith to believe.
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Here is faith to believe. Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Come!
He says his manhood has been restored.
The manhood that has been restored should not go to the street.
Bring him out.
Please, help your neighbour around you.
Bring them out.
In the name of Jesus!
Move.
I command you to be set free, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Be set free, in the name of Jesus!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You fibroid - come out!
I command that cancer, diabetes, hypertension - whatever in your kidneys, liver, blood - out!
Out!
Go to the gallery; there are many people there.
Go up. Bring them out.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You cannot leave here and remain the same.
Confess along with me.
That disease, infirmity - wherever it is located - right now, command it out!
Bring them out.
Say, "No" to sickness.
Say, "No" to infirmity.
I say, "No".
Say, "No".
Wherever it is located, say, "No!"
Say, "No!"
No!
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Say, "No!"
Wherever it is located, say, "No!"
In the name of Jesus!
Say, "No!"
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Bring them out from the gallery.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen. You can see blood substances - what they have been vomiting out.
That is the power of God Almighty flushing out all the poisonous substances in their system.
Whatever challenges - you are released, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
So, the evidence of testimony.
You would know you are delivered before you leave here.
Tell your neighbour, "I'm delivered!"
I can't hear you.
I'm delivered!
Overflow Congregation
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Right now, begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus!
In His blood, there is deliverance.
In His blood, there is healing.
In His blood, there is salvation.
Begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Whatever that are not of God, purge them out, wash them out, in the name of Jesus!
Blood of Jesus!
Cover yourself.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I cover you with the blood of Jesus!
Be covered with the blood of Jesus!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
We are still in an atmosphere of healing and deliverance.
That cancer, wherever it is located in your body - be it in your blood, breast, kidneys, liver, fluids, bones -
wherever it is located, I command it to cease, in the name of Jesus!
Cease!
You cancer, cease, in the name of Jesus!
I command that pain to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Every symptom associated with cancer, cease, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Symptoms associated with cancer, cease, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever name they call that pain -
be it HIV, hypertension - open your lips and begin to command it to cease.
Command it to cease!
The pain associated with it - command it to cease!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Give thanks to God for your freedom.
Right now, remember you country, your nation.
Whatever you have as a contact, raise it up.
God's intervention!
Prayer!
Remember your leader.
Ask God to redeem your leader.
Redeem my leader, Lord!
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Redeem my leader!
God's intervention!
Ask the Lord to redeem your leader.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear you.
Amen.
Again and again.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Now, your freedom has come!
Now, the way out for you has come!
Listen to that.
Now, your freedom has come!
Now, the way out for you has come!
Now, it is time to submit yourself as a channel of God.
Wherever you find yourself from now on, you are a channel of God.
Tell your neighbour, "Wherever I find myself - East, South, West, North - I am a channel of Jesus Christ".
A channel of light, love, forgiveness, faithfulness and obedience.
Bow down your head now.
For those who are just coming to Christ and those who want to rededicate themselves,
say after me: Lord Jesus, come and abide in me.
Wash me with Your precious blood.
Make me Your channel - Your channel of love where there is hate.
Make me Your channel - Your channel of faithfulness where there is unfaithfulness.
Make me Your channel - Your channel of forgiveness where there is unforgiveness.
Make me Your channel - Your channel of pardon where there is injury.
Thank You, Lord, for dying in my place.
Thank You for Your salvation, in Jesus Christ's name.
Amen.
I can't hear your amen.
Thy Kingdom come,
Thy will be done.
The way out for you has come.
Amen.
Tell your neighbour, "I am a channel, a channel of God".
Where there is hatred, I am a channel of love.
Where there is unforgiveness, sin, I am a channel of forgiveness.
I am a channel of God where there is love, love of God.
In Jesus' name.
Amen. Wave your hand.
Hallelujah!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
RV: Mel Flowers 16/06/2018